>> Kyle Simpson: 有些人无疑看到了 WAT
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Some of you
have undoubtedly seen the WAT
我多次提到的视频
video I referred to multiple times,
WAT 视频的其中一个着名的东西是，怎么可能
and one of the famous things in the WAT
video was, how could something like
一个空想的阵列能被强迫等同于否定自己吗
an empty array somehow be coercively
equal to the negation of itself?
而在它的表面上，这个问题的构造方式，
And on its surface,
the way that problem is constructed,
它似乎是针对 JavaScript 的一个明确的参数
it seems like a clear arguments
against JavaScript, and
对双重平等的明确论点
a clear arguments against
the double equals.
但这并不像现在看来不是这样
But this is not as it seems,
this is not as it appears,
因为这个建筑是一个造假的建筑
because this construct is
a false construct to begin with.
在任何情况下你永远都不会
You would never, under any circumstances,
将价值与自身的否定相比较
compare a value to the negation of itself,
ever.
这在节目里是永远不会发生的
That's just never gonna
happen in the programs.
所以我们去找
So we went and looked for
这种人为的情境永远不会发生在真正的代码中
this artificial scenario that
would never happen in real code.
然后说这整个机制被打破了因为一个奇怪的角落
And then said this whole mechanism is
broken because one weird corner case
没有理智的行为
doesn't behave sensibly.
在什么情况下你会有一个阵列
Under what circumstances would
you ever have an array, and
然后尝试将其与数组的求反进行比较 ?
then try to compare it to
the negation of the array?
是否有任何数组的否定，而不仅仅是它本身 ?
Negation of any array,
not just itself, of any array?
这种情况永远不会发生，你绝对不会设计这样的代码。
That would never sensibly occur,
you would never design code like that.
不过，让我们来解释它是如何运作的。
Nevertheless, let's explain how it works.
它会用我教过你的一模一样的东西
It's gonna use the exact same
stuff I already taught you.
如果我有两个阵列还有一些奇怪的原因
If I had two arrays, and
for some strange reason,
我尝试将一个数组与否定本身进行比较。
I tried to compare one array
to the negation of itself.
>> Kyle Simpson: 请将您的考虑中的内容与更合适的比较进行比较，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Compare that in your
mind to the more appropriate comparison,
就是说，我想看看它们不是同一个阵列。
which is to say, I want to check to
see if they're not the same array.
这不是平等的
That's the not equals.
这些可能看起来是一样的，但这些是完全不同的方法。
Those might look like the same thing, but
these are entirely different approaches.
有人说我想知道它是否被强迫等于它的否定
One is saying I wanna see if it is
coercively equal to its negation, and
另一个是说我想知道这不是强迫的
the other one is saying I wanna
see if it is not coercively equal.
这些都是不同的野兽
Those are entirely different beasts.
第 8 行是您要以明智的方式编写代码的第 8 行。
Line 8 is what you would
write in code sensibly.
第 4 行， WAT 视频源，本质上是你永远不会写的代码。
Line 4, the WAT video source, essentially,
is what you would never write in code.
但让我们暂时放纵一下吧
But let's just indulge it for a moment.
为了解释算法我们如何解释第 4 行允许它
To explain the algorithm, how are we gonna
explain that line four allows it and
第 8 行允许吗
also line eight allows it?
这两种情况怎么可能都是真的呢 ?
How is it possible that
both of those can be true?
这就是游戏的算法
Well, here's the algorithm at play.
第一，我们从讲习班开始，一个学生没有，或者
Number one, we start with
the workshop one students not, or
等于拒绝了两个学生的修修期
equal to the negation of
the workshop two students.
我们要做的是减少员工的价值，
What we have to do is reduce
workshop1Students to its value,
是一个数组，然后否定 workshop2Students，
which is an array, and
then negate workshop2Students,
workshop2Students 是一个真实的数组。
workshop2Students is
an array which is truthy.
所以如果我们否定它变成了第五行，它就变成了错误，对吗 ?
So if we negate it becomes line five,
it becomes false, right?
现在，我们有一个非原始的比较原始的。
Now, we have a non-primitive
compared to a primitive.
所以我们需要把这个非原始的变成一个原始的。
So we need to turn that
non-primitive into a primitive.
我们需要把这个阵列变成一个原始的，它变成了什么 ?
We need to turn the array into
a primitive and what does it become?
它会变成空字符串。
It becomes the empty string.
现在，我们的字符串为空，而为 false。
So now,
we have an empty string compared to false.
我们有两个原语，但它们不是同一类型。
We have two primitives but
they are not of the same type.
算法更倾向于两者都变成数字
The algorithm prefers that
they both become numbers, so
这只会变成一个数字它不应该
this one becomes a number,
which it shouldn't.
但是它变成了零而不是纳米，这个要变成
But it does become the number zero instead
of nano and this one needs to become
一个数字，现在 0 等于 0 ，好吗 ?
a number as well and
now zero is equal to zero, okay?
该算法得到了合理应用，但
The algorithm is sensibly applied, but
在一个假的角落里你的密码里不会有这种情况
it's on a bogus corner case that would
never actually happen in your code.
因此，这不是反对这个机制的有效论据。
So it's not an effective
argument against this mechanism.
它制作了伟大的视频和头条新闻
It makes for great videos and
great headlines but
这不是理性的争论。
it is not a rational argument.
第二个更理性，因为如果我们看等价的
The second one is much more rational,
because if we look at the equivalent
不等于，就像否定强迫性的平等。
of the not equals, it is basically like
the negation of the coercive equality.
所以我们可以问自己这是否有意义
So we can ask ourselves,
does it make sense for
与两个学生的作坊相比，一个学生要被胁迫吗 ?
workshop one students to be coercively
compared to workshop two students?
既然他们都是列阵
Well, since they're both arrays,
那么我们实际上正在进行的是一个身份的问题。
then what we're effectively doing
is asking an identity question.
我们是说他们不是同一个身份吗
We're saying,
are they not the same identity?
这对你而言是件很有效的事
Which is a totally valid thing for
you to ask in your program.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 如果你用三等
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: And it would work
identically if you use the triple equals
他们的版本
version of them.
这是理性的事情
It's a rational thing, and
本方法具有结构简单，使用方便，结构简单，使用方便，结构简单，使用方便等问题。
it has no difference in the rational case
between double equals and triple equals.